"TORRENTE
THE DUMB ARM OF THE LAW"
- Luisito!
- Torrente!
- What's it gonna be?
- The usual.
Another?
Yeah.
Another.
Jesus...
Another?
Sure.
Got the time?
Midnight. One more?
No.
I've just started my shift.
"El Fary". Numero 1.
Kids!
What a circus!
Love, little love-birds.
Check out the playground!
It's a zoo! Ha, ha!
Hey, bitch!
Fuck! Blackie!
That son of a bitch!
Hey! Blackie!
Come here!
I've told you,
No street dealing!
Got to eat, Mr Torrente.
- For drugs?
- I swear that...
Don't swear, for Chrisssake!
What's all this?
It's mine!
Sandwiches! Cans!
You're hopeless!
I'm feeling good.
I won't arrest you.
But you need a lesson.
Give me your finger!
- No!
- The little one!
No, please!
I'm confiscating this.
Still pals, eh?
Whiskey in coke!
A little fuel for the body.
Where're you going?
Asshole! Cripple!
Good kids!
Atleti! Atleti!
Viva Atleti!
Come on guys!
That's my Atleti!
The bastards!
Another sip!
Me? Talking to me?
You talking to me?
Rafi!
Me, eh?
You're dead!
Rafi!
What's up, Mom?
Is your head in the clouds?
They sent us
double mackerel!
I'll be right down!
Now! Not next week!
Here you go!
Ooooh!
A Llama revolver,
CGT 38 special!
Goes through 3mm of steel
at a distance of 90m!
Made in Spain.
Who the fuck are you?
The new neighbor.
The fish seller's.
You like guns?
Wanna try it?
Yeah!
Buy one!
Wow! A Llama revolver!
Dad! Dad! Dad!
What? What's the matter?
I'm back.
That's why you woke me?
In case you were worried.
Son of...!
Whitebait! Sardines!
Fish for sale! Whitebait!
Tasty fish!
Hake! Hake for sale!
Get your fish here!
Always in the way!
Cool it, "Van Damme"!
Hey! Watch out!
Luisito, take it easy!
You'll knock it down.
What a cutie!
- How old is he?
- Five.
He's so cute!
Hear the lady, Luis?
Let's see him!
You like kids?
Yes.
Wanna make one?
Silly idiot!
Don't hit him.
Mom!
Sorry ladies!
Some people have hemorrhoids,
I have my kids!
What a pain!
- You too, niece!
- What?
Cover your assets!
If you're gonna work here!
Out!
In the way.
- Move!
- You move!
Hey, ease up... That hurts.
Shut up, Dad!
Fix the suspension!
I'll fix your chassis too!
What a treasure!
Off to work, Dad!
Put the "H" in
handicapped for me.
Like I don't know
howto spell.
That's the idea. Look
pathetic.
You'll get some sun here.
- You're fucking hand!
- What hand!
Twist it. Look more handicapped!
I can move it sometimes.
Don't even try it!
Stay here till you get
what we said.
Felipe!
How's business?
Tough. Pretty tough.
Let's see if... Excuse me.
Spare some change,
for the love of God!
Hey! I'm worse off.
- Hit the floor!
- It's a hold-up!
Give him the cash!
Put it here!
I got a gun on you!
Move!
- Dumb fuck!
- Move!
I'll shoot you! You ass!
I'll fucking shoot!
Hand it over! I'll...
- We told you!
- Hand it over!
Don't shout!
My cousin's crazy!
I'll blow your head off!
Stop screaming!
I blasted you!
Tony, what's up bro?
We've got a tasty stewtoday.
Throw in some meat for once!
Bit of protein.
Come on fatso, move it!
Cheers, guys!
Come here, kid.
Put some leftovers in
a bag for the dog.
Leftovers?
The ones on the tables!
Dickhead!
Neighborhood's a nightmare.
No shit.
Chinks everywhere.
Thanks to the new restaurant
on the corner.
Chinks, Arabs, blacks.
Madrid's disgusting.
Here you are.
Here you go!
A quick whisky.
You owe me 6,000 pesetas.
But, I've been a
regular for ten years.
- 6,000 pesetas ib whiskeys.
- Fucking hell!
I'm not going to emigrate!
Pay by tomorrow or...
- What?
...find somewhere else.
All right, then.
Get lost!
I'll close you down!
Out! Get lost!
Come here, kid.
Sorry, but
your gun's like your cock.
Not everyone can touch it!
Sure!
That chick's your girlfriend?
No, she's my cousin
from the village.
- She's a slut.
- A slut?
She looks clean.
She's one of those
"nympho-manics".
- What's your name, son?
- Rafael Jimenez Valera.
- Rafi, to my friends.
- Rafi.
- Do you like guns?
- Yeah.
Early on Sundays
I go to the park to
shoot at a few cans.
Wow!
- Fresh air and gunpowder.
- Cool!
- Wanna come?
- Where do you live?
- Upstairs, first floor.
And me the second.
You and I'll go far.
Bah. Adds taste.
Dad!
Food's ready.
I want a sandwich.
I want a ham sandwich.
Sute, and caviar too.
It's not Christmas yet!
Smells great.
How much did you get?
It's... well... times are hard.
You can tell things are bad.
Fucking useless!
- Not cheating me, are you?
- No.
Want a body search?
No, no, no.
I kept this
for cigarettes.
You bastard! The doctor
told you not to smoke.
Just a few drags.
No way! Health comes first.
Now eat this up.
I hate washing up!
Bon appetit.
Mr Torrente!
Blackie!
Why aren't you in bed like
all good black boys?
I'm here with some cousins
to thank you for being so nice.
All in the call of duty.
Cool it!
It's OK. Easy, friends.
Don't get upset.
Come on. Look at the chop!
Here's a nice chop.
Come and get it!
Come on! Go for it!
What?
It's Sunday. Remember?
Sunday...
Fresh air, gunpowder.
A few shots...
what you said.
Fuck you!
Kid!
Where's your cousin?
Did you want her?
Next time, bring her
to set up the cans.
You first.
For this you need class,
it's not like selling shrimp!
Shit! Beginner's luck!
Watch the maestro!
You broke the bridge.
Me? No!
I told you,
your gun's like your cock.
Now it needs fixing.
- Are you good at shooting?
- Idiot!
Top in my class.
I was one helluva cop
in charge of hundred men.
And?
In Spain, it's a crime
to be a good cop.
I had enemies.
I was put on patrol.
Like a rookie!
- Sorry.
- Not to worry.
I got my informers.
With the right case, I'll be...
back on top. Wanna see what's
in the case?
- Suppose so.
- OK!
- See!
- A MP28 Smitzer!
They're not made now.
Watch it cans!
Here's Torrente!
What are you nuts?
What? Am I annoying you?
Christ! My kids are playing here!
The outdoors belong to everybody.
Beat it!
If you don't stop, I'll call
the police. You asshole!
Come again!
Asshole!
Listen shit-face,
I am the police.
What the...?
Here, Manolito!
Dumb shit!
Screwed up our fun. Let's go!
They didn't admit me.
Because I wear glasses.
They need the glasses.
You're cut out for the force.
You still want to join?
Of course!
To carry a gun all day and use it!
And they pay you for it!
That'd be heaven.
Done. I'll sort it out.
What do you do at night?
Sleep.
Queer's stuff.
You're coming on patrol.
You mean it?
I'll turn you into Chuck Norris!
Here's a tidbit.
Some cockles. You're in
the police, I hear.
The secret police.
So was my late husband.
He was a caretaker before.
Then came the robbery.
And the end.
But I don't want to bore you.
Thanks.
- Have a cockle. They're great!
- Thanks.
Your family and your
business are safe
with me.
- You're a jewel!
- Yes, he is.
Amparo!
We've got a visitor!
Sorry.
Don't worry.
You're lovely.
- Always in the way.
- Rafi!
Jose Luis Torrente.
Here for your every need.
Excuse me.
My niece, excuse her. You
know girls nowadays.
So casual!
Only think of themselves.
Howtimes have changed!
- The WC?
- I'll straighten it up.
No need, don't worry.
Second on the left.
Hi! I'm Pili. I have...
Wanna be pals?
Get away! Off, off!
So clean you could
drink out of it.
So theatrical! Amparo, ready?
Yes.
It's my nephew's wedding.
He's a Hare Krishna.
At least it's in a church.
Lunch sometime?
I'll hold you to that.
I'll leave you in peace.
See you later.
Bye!
Fine whitebait and sardines!
- The money? Get lost!
- What's up?
Antonio, bah!
Fucking hell!
Chinkie!
Chinkie! Come here!
- What's this shit?
- Sweet and sour pork.
It tastes like a crust
with jam on.
And these, for playing drums?
Gimme a fork!
Take it away!
Bring bread!
Right.
Chinkie!
Are you pulling my leg?
Bamboo shoots.
For pandas!
Yes.
Am I a panda?
No!
The bread?
There is none.
No bread!
I can't believe it!
The manager!
I want to see the manager!
He's complaining all the time.
He's crazy.
- What's up?
- He keeps complaining.
- What do we do?
- Out!
Throw him out!
Hey, a bit of bread.
Torrente!
Carlitos!
What're you doing?
On guard, as always.
Eyes peeled.
Seen anything?
Depends, ha, ha.
Carlitos!
- Do you like parole?
- All right.
All right.
The Chinese.
Bikes keep going
in and out all night.
You don't say!
Yeah, I can smell a rat.
The sweet and sour.
No scraps of food, either.
Very odd.
Right. They use it all.
I bet they buy bad meat
and bring it in at night.
To avoid the authorities.
But tonight...
the shit will come down.
Tonight...
we've got a job.
Got to be strong.
Really strong!
Don't you drink?
No, with "Aikido"
there's no cigarettes,
drink, drugs...
Aikido's got no fucking idea.
What?
On long nights, you need a
boost.
Or you run out of gas.
Want some?
Drugs, right?
Damn right.
But it's bad.
What's bad about it?
Here's a drug.
Does it bite?
Scratch?
Grab your balls?
What's so bad?
Hi, I'm a drug addict.
Sorry to bother you...
This is evil.
This is shit.
Luisito.
Put this on credit.
I'll take a piss.
Your hands?
After.
After? Look, kid.
Some men washem before they piss.
Some wash after.
I wash before. Why?
My cock is sacred.
It should be worshipped.
It's the earth's core,
the hosepipe to happiness.
Do the same.
Yes, yes.
All the excrescence...
and microbes out there mean...
you've got to respect your cock.
I get fucked off with queers who...
act as if their cocks were filthy.
What a python! Fine weapon, son.
Thanks.
You ever fucked?
Fucked?
Yeah. Screwed a slut.
- No.
- You serious?
I've seen it in films.
Hollywood musicals?
Pussies are to eat not to see.
Who cares!
How can you patrol with me
if you've never been laid!
No one'll respect you.
But local girls...
Nonsense! Changed your undies?
Yesterday.
Good enough.
Smell the women!
You're gonna flip.
Checked the talent?
Over there.
Check out...
the whores!
Come on!
The biggest slut of all.
Scram, midget!
Papa Smurf's looking for you!
Milagritos, princess!
Look who I've brought.
Is the circus in town or
are the monkeys loose?
Don't scare him.
He's got a problem.
Only one?
Bitch, he's losing the urge.
Milagritos, I give you a boy.
Make him a man.
Come on! Upstairs, "Bubbles".
And act like a cop!
Girls! Dinner's here!
What never gonna
take your clothes off?
I'm embarrassed.
Do you want me to do it?
- It's er...
- Shit!
Get a move on!
I'm paid by the hour.
So you've never made love?
No...
I've seen it in films.
Oh, how sweet!
What a baby! Maybe it'll
freak you out.
Come closer.
They won't bite.
Come on tiger!
You like them, eh?
Don't you?
Get dressed.
Wasn't so hard, was it?
Not a word to the fat guy!
That was quick. Enjoy it?
Delicious, eh!
Now, that's a man. What a hunk!
Champ! She's got
great hands, eh kid?
Yeah, sure has.
And my money?
It's on me.
Got five thousand?
Yeah, my allowance.
Look, you've had a ball.
It's no time for skimping.
Hand it over! Here, Milagritos.
Problem is you gotta pay 'em.
Your cock's a happy camper!
Bye girls!
Naughty girl!
Bad luck girls,
Torrente's leaving.
This is the place.
Now we watch
for anything weird.
This is the worst part.
Waiting for things to happen.
Wanna jerk off?
What?
Jerk each other off.
You and me?
Of course!
Now?
For fun. You stroke me...
and I stroke you.
Just to relax, no queer shit.
Nothing queer.
I don't know if I can now.
Pull it out! To kill time.
You can't park here.
- Why?
- It's private.
The street?
It's our street. It's
not for fat queers.
Listen to him.
You're wrong, dude.
Look...
I'm going cause I feel like it.
You gonna let them bully us?
Easy, kid. Got to lead them on.
Five chinks on bikes.
Doing home deliveries.
At four a.m.!
Something's up, kid.
I smell it.
I don't like the atmosphere here.
I like the square near the market
or where I can see
all the young schoolgirls.
You're a dirty old man!
And too choosy.
- See that Chinese?
- Yes.
Watch for anything strange.
Keep your eye on it.
Dad!
Come on, guy. It's nothing.
What a shame!
Hang in there!
So the insurance covers it?
Don't worry about that now!
See Amparito, all my life
caring for my Dad.
Go upstairs and rest.
We can only pray now.
I'm devastated. When I go up
it'll really hit me.
Cheer up!
I'll keep you company and...
bring you a meal.
How's that?
I'd love that. You're an angel,
Amparito.
Amparito! Come in!
You look sensational!
Wow! Fish! Smells great!
I've tidied up a bit.
You deserve it - and more.
Delicious! I'm bursting!
- Thanks.
- Thanks to you.
It was fantastic.
I'm glad you liked it.
Beautiful! Clean!
And can cook!
The ideal woman!
Don't exaggerate.
If I married, it'd be
to someone like you.
Amparito.
I've something for you.
What?
It's a surprise.
Do you like it?
- Well?
- Is it for me?
Of course! I only
know one Amparito.
I'm speechless.
Say nothing. "El Goyanes"
did it for me.
Charged me a fortune.
It's embarrassing...
But I kept them.
Damn!
They're my aunt's.
Christ!
She's been looking for them.
Fuck!
You're too old to play the fool.
Too old?
- I'm a kid.
- Right.
Whose are these lovely tits?
Hands off!
Don't be a tease!
I'll put some music on.
Little devil!
Finished?
You liked it, eh?
As you said, one of
my best fucks ever.
- Without paying, that is.
- What!
The door, sorry.
- Torrente.
- Rafi!
- Am I interrupting?
- You always do.
Anyway, we might
end up family.
I came to remind
you about the job.
Shit! Work! Duty calls,
darling!
- What?
- Before you go
clean up a bit, will you.
Boy, did I turn your cousin on!
She's a tigress.
Your father... Was it them?
Remember the special case
I needed to get back to the top?
We just need to get in.
- The restaurant?
- That's just a front!
- You want to go now?
- Yes! Let's go!
Just us two?
Scared? Forget it.
I don't need you.
No, I'll go anywhere with you.
It's the goons at the door.
Yes, they've seen us now.
They know my car.
Is the fish van yours?
Yes.
Get the keys.
I can't because my
Mom's paying it off.
It's only for deliveries.
This is insubordination!
Move your ass! Get the keys!
Fuck!
Torrente, the goons!
Shit!
What do we do?
Evening!
Good work.
An entrance.
This way!
It's a bit dark.
Come on! Don't be scared.
You first. I'll cover you.
Shit! Shit!
Come on!
There's some light.
Keep close
so nothing happens to you.
Where's the spring roll?
No idea.
Look, I'm a...
calm, reasonable man.
Sometimes I lose my temper.
I'm behaving myself today.
Really, I don't know.
Then why do I feel you're
putting one over on me?
Leave me alone, please.
Is that a Chinese
fable or what?
I don't know nothing.
Chinese fables are
for kids. And dickheads.
Please.
- Am I a kid?
- No.
- Do I look like a dickhead?
- No, no.
- See? You're insulting me.
- I don't know anything.
And that hurts.
Understand?
I'm a good China man.
Let me go!
Tell him, Israel.
Please leave me.
It wasn't me.
Honestly.
That's what pisses me
off the most.
His yelling.
Chink!
Stop yelling!
Stop it!
Fuck, what a bloody mess!
You've got one last chance.
You're one of us.
- He knows howto torture.
- He learnt going to movies.
Of course.
That's about it.
No, no.
The party's over.
Clean this.
You, back to work!
Has my uncle phoned? Mendoza?
- Yes, good news.
- Has Farrelli done it?
Yes. The whole cache
for 50 million.
Is that all?
50 million!
It can't be top quality.
You've never seen
heroin like this!
We'll be kings!
It's worth ten times that.
Great!
- When's it coming?
- Wednesday night.
Our night with
the transvestites.
Well, put it off!
Let's split.
Your hands, kid. The prints.
They could kill us for less.
Not one clue!
Let's go!
Help me.
One, two, three.
Push. Push a bit more.
Come on, kid.
- Motherfuckers!
- Shit! Run, kid!
Stop there!
Motherfuckers!
The bikes! Get the...
the bikes.
Come on, run.
Shit!
Some bikes are after us.
Drive faster!
You. Overtake them.
Easy. I know Madrid like
the back of my hand.
Step on it!
Shit! The van won't go
any faster.
Jesus Christ!
- Fuck!
- They're shooting at us.
Calm down!
We're fucked! The bastards!
We're going down
a one-way street.
Here we go!
Step on it!
We shouldn't have gone.
Stop shitting on yourself!
They're gonna hit us.
They're still there.
One sharp turn
and I'll lose 'em.
- What's this?
- It's cut off.
This wasn't here before.
Built with taxpayers' money.
They've got off.
We've got to think of something.
We're going to die.
Step on the gas!
- Yeah! That's it!
- We're saved.
"And the mommy duck
had four lovely ducklings
but when the last one hatched
what an ugly duckling!
When they went swimming,
all the farm animals stared.
Yes?
Sorry, but we have a problem.
I've told you not to ring here.
Someone got in.
Shit! The Colombians?
Colombians?
No, a fat guy and a retard.
Two strangers.
They don't look professional.
I don't like it at all.
Pack up. We'll set up
again after the drop.
Will do.
- What's wrong?
- Our story?
They cooked the ugly duckling
in a restaurant with orange.
It doesn't end like that.
It ends the way Dad fucking wants.
Go to sleep!
It was horrible.
Is your mouth pasty?
How did you know?
Just like my first dead body.
They're incredible. They
killed the Chink.
The worst is when Mom
finds out about the van.
But that's what insurance is for.
We need to call reinforcements.
You what?
We need reinforcements.
Forget that.
Do you want a clever dick
to ruin it?
- It's the case of the century.
- What then?
We may need people.
But normal people. Patriots!
I've got friends
I play pool and
go to gym with. Tomorrow
there's a roleplay game.
I can ask them.
Are they like you?
What do you mean?
- Rafi!
- Look who I brought.
Hi boys!
I'm Torrente. Rafi told
me you're tough cookies.
Malaguita, watch it!
This is Torrente.
- The dude with the machine gun?
- Fuck me!
What's up?
Don't you know who I am?
Yeah. A pile of shit.
Respect! I'm armed.
Let's go outside.
I need you to help Rafi and me.
Why should we follow a fat pig
like you?
Toneti! I'll crack you one!
He can't walk in like that.
No manners. Dirty prick.
- "Lightbulb", respect!
- Boys!
You're annoying me.
Watch it. I can turn.
Hey, sonny.
What?
You p-p-pushed me.
- So?
- Nothing.
Just take care, please.
If you don't mind.
You're dead,
you fuckhead.
Take that!
There! All on my own.
What's up, Michelin Man?
Don't you know who I am?
You're Policarpo Diaz,
The best boxer in Europe.
Fifty eight KO's.
You'll be world champ, too.
Torrente says so.
You know all about me
and you dig Atletico.
Out please. Christ, what a
riot!
Let's go, guys.
Hey, Sultan! You'd get a bundl
e for fighting in the ring.
What a beating!
God, you're heavy.
We're going to make history.
With little training.
Count on us.
I need to know you better.
To see your talents. I'll
make men out of you.
What's up? Not interested
in what I'm saying?
What can you do?
I'm an expert on 007.
What's that?
- An erotic hot line?
- No, a super spy!
I know. James Bond,
the greatest... after me.
I've worked for the CIA.
Told you.
He's dating my cousin.
What I like about espionage
are the computers.
"Lightbulb" is bright.
He's a student.
Of electronics.
It's good having an
intellectual with us.
Malaguita's...
- a brown belt.
- I'll soon get black.
He's seen all the films -
Jackie Chan, Bruce Lee and Mar...
Dakastros, Mar Dakastros,
the new martial arts star.
Seen "The strongest sun"?
Rings a bell.
Fucking sit down!
You're drawing attention.
Fucking hell! Fuck!
Keep tabs on your kids
or I'll get in trouble.
Sorry, Manolo. Another whisky.
At your age I was agile too.
And I didn't mince around.
I was all muscle.
But karate
and Jujitsu can't compete
with a kick in the balls.
Nobody can kick me
in the balls.
From a lateral position,
masking the waist and a
twist of the hip.
Demonstration!
Take your best shot, Torrente.
Malaguita's all mouth, eh?
- No. Try him.
- I'll waste you.
You won't. I know how.
With concentration,
this posture
sits the genitals
and the scrotum
in the peritoneum.
You're as hard as wood.
Watch where I put his scrotum!
Bingo!
- Torrente, out!
- OK, Manolo. Let's go!
Out! They'll pay you
at the entrance.
This place
is a modern shit-hole.
Torrente, my winnings?
We have 12,000 left. That'll
get you nowhere.
I'll look after it.
Another one, love.
Those chicks turn me on.
- Waitresses?
- No, the pregnant ones.
I think about
them getting fucked.
They spread their legs and
had a prick up them. A dollop of
sperm got left inside.
If not, how did they get
knocked up?
It makes me fucking horny.
Torrente, let's go over there.
These chicks love it up the ass.
But they're so young.
- That one's only 13.
- Or 14.
You're a fussy bunch.
When they start having periods,
they're ready to go.
I'm going to phone my mom.
She might be worried.
Go on, mamma's boy.
Here's what's happening.
We're after some global
drug dealers.
They're getting a stash
of pure heroin.
We've been in their lab,
their HQ.
We know when it'll be
but we don't know where.
We have to find out.
Here're the whiskies.
- Pussy!
- Asshole!
Ooh! Listen to her!
Good news!
Your dad's back home.
Great, right, but...
now we've got to focus
on the plan.
Boss,
I can get a mike in.
A mike or a person.
That calls for 007.
Yes! By targeting a mobile
on your mike
we can all listen in.
That's howto find out.
Perfect! There's the plan.
Tomorrow'll be great!
Right we are!
Whisky's packed with vitamins.
Your buddies are a gas.
Evening, Torrente and company.
- Carlitos
- Can I sit down?
If you can reach.
What a game you missed!
Atletico beat the shit out
of Real Madrid. 4-1.
Right on. Give me your scarf.
I'd die...
for Atletico.
You're in luck.
There's nothing better than
working with Torrente.
The man you're
looking at is the tops!
Here's a lottery ticket
for you and for all of you.
Nice one Carlitos! Turn round.
My eyes are still peeled.
Oing on: :
Sure, sure.
Watch yourself!
Torrente,
- This is two days old.
- Yes, that dwarf's
tricky but he's blind too.
Another round?
Let's go to "Danch" The music's
- dynamite.
- "Danch"?
Maybe they'd let us in with you.
I could get you into
the Royal Palace. No problem!
Play some good music, kid!
You can't stand here! What's
that shit?
Get lost! Leave me alone!
Don't talk like that
about "El Fary"!
Take that!
"Vaya torito, hay torito guapo"
"tiene botines"
Get out, shit!
Viva El Fary!
Torrente!
Lucky I wasn't in a
fighting mood.
Did you see me hit him?
Let's go to a bar
with some bimbos.
Sorry but I have to go.
- I've got to work tomorrow.
- So do we.
To work! Get Spain moving!
Fuck it!
Come on Rafi!
I've got to work too.
Tomorrow we've got to follow
our plan. Let's go home.
Go with your pals.
In case they get lost.
- Come on, Torrente.
- Get lost!
See you tomorrow.
Kids!
Real Madrid, Champions!
We were unlucky.
4 - fucking - 1.
Another one.
Don't drink anymore,
Torrente.
Come on, last one.
No more. Go home.
- Have one with me.
- No.
- Are we friends or not?
- Yes, I'm your friend.
- But this is too much.
- Luisito, fuck it. Come on.
Give me another.
- No!
- Luisito!
It's true, you are back!
- How are you?
- Hello, kid.
Look. Aren't they lovely?
Yeah, not bad.
Make a few. We'll sell them.
No, they're for me.
My bicycles.
You're going senile.
Not working today?
No. The whole day's
for making bicycles.
OK. You've been sick.
Sick, that's a joke!
Don't go yet.
What're you doing, idiot?
Since I ate that stuff
my balance is better.
I walk and I feel better.
The neighbors can see!
Sit down!
If the social worker finds
out, we're shit.
Then what do we do for cash?
Don't get up again.
- Dad!
- What?
I think I can sell the bikes.
Go on, make me a few.
Fuck you!
Hello!
Anybody here?
We're all here.
Everything OK, guys?
Great! The sound's shitty
but it picks up fine.
- Wasn't there anything bigger?
- It's the latest model.
Well, a T-shirt will cover it.
The plan is to go to the
restaurant and
ask for the boss. Say
you've come from
Farrelli to confirm
details of the drop.
So I give Farrelli some details.
No, no. You confirm details.
You've come from Farrelli.
So I confirm details.
And don't forget to
find out where the drop is.
Right, so I go there...
Push the button. Don't forget.
I push the button and say
I'm from... Manilli?
Farrelli! Farrelli!
To confirm details.
Farrelli wants to know
where the details are.
Place of the drop. Right.
Any questions?
- No.
- Do you want me to go?
I don't know.
I can react to danger.
Demonstration.
- What's he up to?
- Malaguita!
The body of Christ.
- Yes.
- Mendoza.
It's the Frenchman.
We await instructions.
Farrelli's rung. It's
tonight at the old warehouse.
- Is it all ready?
- Yes.
Any more on that scum?
Not yet, sir.
I'll take precautions.
I want everyone ready. OK?
- Everyone ready.
- Of course.
Those cunts won't spoil
my business.
The body of Christ.
- You can go in.
- Thanks.
Good luck, kid!
One thing I don't understand...
Why's he got a mike? He can
tell us when he's back.
It's better first hand.
And who says
he'll be coming back?
Go in, kid.
Afternoon.
Come in.
You're from Farrelli.
Yes, I'm one of Farrelli's men.
He sent me
to find out the place for the
drop. Of the drugs.
Have some candy.
Thanks.
Sit down.
Can I have two? My mom says
sugar's good for the brain.
Toneti's a bit dim.
Of course!
A kid who takes notice
of his mom won't have problems.
Have you been
with Farrelli long?
Yes, well, Manilli, Farrelli
is trying me out.
Over the summer.
I'm on a grant.
Good.
How is Farrelli?
Is he still in Segovia?
Overdosing on pork?
Yes, he stuffs his face.
Really? That's great.
Told you. He's not gone veggie.
Lightbulb, the sound is crap!
What's that?
To listen to the game with.
I'll tear out your eyes.
Torrente sent me.
He's a sneak.
Tell us more.
Tell him where I live!
He's Rafi's friend. He's
dating Rafi's cousin.
Bastard!
I'm too young...
to die.
Stop!
Toneti! Shit!
- Toneti!
- What's happened?
Get rid of him!
I don't want a trace!
He's dead! He's dead!
Shit, Torrente!
What a bummer!
Don't be pansies.
You knew what was coming.
This isn't "Bambi"!
But he was our friend.
He was soft.
Giving my name so fast.
They were gonna torture him.
Torture him? So what?
I was in the desert
with the Africa Corps
It was so hot that we
fried eggs on our jeep.
Scorpions stung our balls.
We had typhoid and cholera.
And the Arabs, who are like
the French but dirtier,
ate everything alive.
Why were we there? Cause we
wouldn't betray a comrade.
We had endurance.
We had endurance, kids.
T-t-Toneti was soft.
- Yes, he was soft.
- Soft.
Could that be
Jose Luis Torrente?
Do you know him?
It didn't seem important
but this morning
I found this.
Rodrigo, you asshole!
- Who hired this guy?
- He's Mendoza's nephew.
Are you thick? Can't you read?
It looked old so...
A cop sneaks in and we
couldn't care less.
Shall I call Padilla?
Yes, he can earn his keep.
You're a moron!
Thickhead!
Officer Padilla!
There are the leaders!
Indurain!
Go for it!
Nobody move!
Get down!
Take a look.
- Where is he?
- Who?
You're very bad to break it.
Where is he?
I've spent all day making them.
Fuck! Where do these people
crawl out of?
No one here.
- What do we do?
- Tie him up.
Darling, it's Amparin.
Not a word! Do you hear?
Right.
Who are you?
A neighbor.
Come to borrow some sugar?
No, to get a tray.
Someone's going
to die for a tray.
Die? I've no idea
what's going on.
I'll do what I have to.
What do you know
about Torrente?
Nothing.
He's my cousin Rafi's friend.
Isn't Torrente
dating the cousin?
Yes.
I'm nobody's girlfriend.
And not his!
- You can kill him.
- You're coming with us.
Yeah!
We need to unwind.
And you've got cute lips.
If you want, I'll suck you off.
That'd help us unwind.
We can do it here.
Get your dicks out!
Hang on! You'll get your fill.
Excuse me!
If she's doing any sucking,
can I
have a bit?
Wash your mouth out, gramps
and put your cock away.
You're a big guy
to be a faggot!
Call me a faggot?
What?
Leave him alone!
Don't hit her!
Hit me!
Show off in front
of your friends!
Pull your gun out and shoot!
If it's not a toy one!
Did you think
I'd get down on my knees?
Like the girl, and say sorry?
The old boy's a real cunt!
Granpa's a champ!
How do you feel, champ?
Wanna fight, gramps?
Come on!
That's right!
Eh, gramps?
Careful, gramps!
Ow! You're hurting me!
Wow!
I was wrong about you.
I thought you were
just assholes
but you're three real bastards!
- Careful.
- I'll kill him.
Leave him. He's scared.
Scared?
Of you?
Grab the girl.
It's terrible about
your father.
Those three men dragged
my poor niece off.
- Bastards!
- They left this.
Stay away scum or she'll die.
The Frenchman.
Scum!
My poor niece kidnapped.
She's a saint.
She's very fond of you.
Fond of me?
She said you're attractive.
Torrente! Look who I've got.
Her!
Chinkie? Remember?
- From the restaurant.
- Yes.
Those men are very bad.
They killed your father
and my boyfriend, Wang.
I want to avenge Wang. I'll
tell you everything.
The drop?
Tonight in the old warehouse.
- It may be a trap!
- No!
I'll go too.
If it's a trap I'll die.
- For my father!
- Yeah!
- For Toneti!
- For Wang!
And for my cousin!
- Come on, kid.
- Go ahead!
- I'll go on the bike.
- Go where you want!
I'm coming too!
The time for justice has arrived.
Here.
Take this.
Gee thanks!
That's the entrance.
Through the back.
Watch out for guards.
Stay here. Watch the vehicles.
- But!
- Torrente.
- Perhaps...
- No buts!
This is no place for women.
The chink was right. Guards.
This might help.
What is it?
A lethal weapon called
"Sun-yu".
- You what?
- Sun-yu, a Ninja star.
Go on. Demonstration!
Nice one! Two shits less.
Get your guns!
Let's go!
Coming!
- Who are you?
- Police.
A few routine questions.
My vase!
Nearly splashed me!
What a mess!
You left it there.
But the case is
with my niece's fiance,
Superintendent Torrente.
Torrente?
Yes.
Jose Luis Torrente?
Do you know him?
What a freak!
Did he say he's in the Force?
What?
He was expelled years ago.
He's nuts.
Ramirez! Leave the cash alone!
- Could be evidence.
- Evidence?
Amparo!
Look what they're
making her do.
Doesn't need much persuading.
Must be the boss.
Careful!
Sir.
You aren't doing things right.
I've brought the money myself.
Because you've made me edgy.
The money!
All under control.
Control?
Why's she here?
It's not a fucking party.
Farrelli's about to arrive.
Take up positions! Quick!
We need the case.
To screw up the operation.
Don't we arrest them?
- That too.
- Look what Lightbulb's got.
- What is it?
- A remote control bomb.
It could be useful.
Great! Did you see the car?
Put it there.
So when Farrelli
comes we'll get him
and block the exit
and stop them escaping.
Fucking go for it!
I fucking will!
Is that Farrelli? Shit!
We'll blow up the cars later.
Carlitos! What've you done!
It's a trap. Clear out!
It's an ambush.
- Now's the time!
- You what?
Don't move! Police!
Police!
Police! Don't move!
Malaguita!
Christ! What chaos!
Now's the time to get the case!
- Go and get the case!
- Why me?
You were the one who
screwed up the bomb.
And you're less to aim at.
Come on Carlitos!
Run! Fucking come on!
The case!
They've got the case!
Carlitos!
Carlitos! Cowards!
The money! We've got the money!
The case is ours! Let's go!
No! And Malaguita
and my cousin?
He's dead. She's a slut.
I've got the cash.
- Come on!
- Leave me!
Are you cray!
We have 50 million.
- I'll give you 10%
- Leave me!
Fuck you then!
This has been
one great fuck-up!
Bring the girl.
If you don't get my money,
you'll have nowhere to hide.
You've got 10 minutes.
I'll be waiting.
You stay here!
"A Llama revolver
38 Special CGT"
"Made in Spain".
Shit!
A rat!
You're gonna pay for this.
Where's the money?
Rafi!
Torrente! You're back!
Here, kid!
Save your cousin.
Go on!
Amparo!
Don't move!
Want your Amparo?
Drop the gun?
Leave it there.
Always in the way.
Kiss your life goodbye!
Christ! This is hell!
Let's go.
Torrente!
Are you all right?
Please,
Make sure they bury my father
the way he lived.
With dignity.
Remember son, that in life
one thing's more important
than being a cop
and that's
being Spanish!
Will he recover?
We were after this gang
for two years.
You did it!
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Just one thing.
The money?
Let's go guys!
To Torremolinos!
Torrente's paying!